

Contacts

Phone: +48 601 618 780

F-mail: krawczakbartek@gmail.com

Tech skills

- нтмі
- CSS
- JavaScript
- PHP
- Mysql, Postgresql, Oracle Database
- Git and Github or Gitlab
- Readmine
- Bootstrap
- Material-UI
- Codeigniter
- Laravel
- · Zend Framework

Other skills

- NodeJS
- React
- Angular
- · Java Spring Boot
- Vite
- Jetbrains
- Docker

DOWNLOAD MY CV

Bartłomiej Krawczak

Junior PHP Developer

My name is Bartłomiej Krawczak. I graduated in computer science from the Catholic University of Lublin. Currently, he has been working as a PHP developer at RSoftStudio for two and a half years, creating software for public clients. I'm working on a document management system there. I introduce corrections and create new functionalities. My specialty is programming. I'm not afraid to learn and use as much technology as I need. Personally, I feel good in front-end technologies such as HTML, CSS, Angular, React. I can also write in back-end technologies such as Laravel, Codeigniter, Zend Framework and PHP.

Projects

All my projects are on Github.

Employment history

Junior PHP Developer - at RSoftStudio

August 2021 - Now

- Document Managment System
 - Zend Framework
 - Porstgresql
 - Jquery
 - EPUAPDocker
- E-Services System
 - Symfony
 - Mysql
 - Docker
- BIP System
 - o Zend Framework
 - o Oracle Database
 - o Jquery
 - Docker
- Archive System
 - Zend Framework
 - Mysql
 - o Jquery
 - Docker
- Delegation System
 - Zend Framework
 - Postgresql
 - o Jquery
 - o Bootstrap
 - Docker

Programmer PHP - Internship at RSoftStudio

December 2020 - February 2021

- Survey Management System
- Document Managment System
- Zend Framework
- Boostrap
- Jquery

Wordpress Developer - Practice Freeline Agencja Interaktywna

June 2020 - July 2020

- Creating an online shop
- Lab client website update
- SEC
- Small fixes for blood donation client website
- Improvement of url addresses

Researcher - Lublin IT Days

October 2016 - June 2019

 $\bullet\,$ Work on the organization of the event.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science, Catholic University of Lublin

October 2016 - June 2019

Master of Computer Science, Catholic University of Lublin

October 2019 - June 2021